# Harsha Vardhan Koneru

## Senior Software Developer

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Able to handle any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 2 years of software experience.

### **Work History**

2020-08 - Senior Software Engineer

**Current** ValueLabs

2019-05 - Software Engineer

2020-07 ValueLabs

2019-01 - Software Intern

2019-03 ValueLabs

2018-04 - Software Intern

2018-06 National Remote Sensing Center

## **Projects**

#### 1. Neiman Marcus

Developed Assistance and Store pages for Neiman Marcus and Bergdorf Goodman.

Role: Front-End Developer
Technology Stack: React

#### My Contributions:

- Migrated the ATG pages to React Pages.
- Written Next.js scripts for server-side rendering

#### 2. Mednax

Analytics dashboard. Portal, where users upload their data sheets at any time, those gets processed by analytics engine and finally stored into analytics data base. Later users open their dashboards to see visualizations, and insights.

Role: Full Stack Developer

Technology Stack: Angular 8, Node JS, Azure Cloud Platform, tableau

#### Contact

#### Address

Hyderabad, Telangana, 500081

#### **Phone**

+91 817-975-3036

#### E-mail

koneru.harsha98@gmail.com

#### **Skills**

Software Development



Development Lifecycles



Analytics



Database Programming



Algorithm Implementation



#### **Education**

2015-08 - 2019-07

## Bachelor of Technology: Computer Science and Engineering

V R Siddhartha Engineering College

Graduated with 9.39 GPA

#### My Contributions:

- Web Portal Designed and developed portal, where users can login, upload and view their dashboards.
- Okta Configured identity provider to portal, where users can login from different sources.
- Tableau Developed scripts and integrated visualizations to portal.
- Web Services Developed Rest API to read data from analytics database.
- Microsoft Azure Used Azure Blob Storage, Azure MSSQL Server, Azure Functions and Azure Virtual Machines'
- Docker Wrote Scripts to Software installations and deployments.

#### 3. Group O

Developed plugin to Testing Framework, this plugin helpful to Azure continuous Server to monitor execution process and get results back to project management tool.

Role: Plugin Developer

Technology Stack: Node JS, Azure Cloud Platform, Java

My Contributions:

- Written Node JS Rest Client to update status to Project management tool.
- Written tool to read logs in node is

#### 4. Shaw Systems

Floor Plan Web APP – Inspection tool, here vehicles get inspected by collecting vehicle current status information. This process will go various steps in workflow process.

Role: Full Stack Developer

Technology Stack: Node JS, Angular, Express JS, MSSQL DB, MongoDB

My Contributions:

• Web Portal development.

Rest API Development

#### 5. Apiture

Developer portal to host open banking APIs and make them available to public users for usage. Users come, try, and later subscribe them for their application integrations.

Role: Full Stack Developer

**Technology Stack:** NodeJS, TypeScript, OpenAPI, Jasmine JS, Karma JS **My Contributions:** 

- Written OPEN API Specifications to define APIs.
- Developed test framework to test Developed APIs.

#### **Publications**

# Invariant Feature based Darknet Architecture for Moving Object classification

Jul 10, 2020

IEEE Sensors Journal

https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/do cument/9138434/

#### Certifications

2017-08

# Python for Everybody Specialization

University of Michigan,

Coursera

2017-09

## Introduction to R for Data Science

Microsoft, edX

2018-02

# Programming with R for Data Science

Microsoft, edX

2018-06

Oracle 12c SQL

**ORACLE Certification Program** 

## 6. Invariant Feature based Darknet Architecture for Moving Object classification

Role: Developer

Technology Stack: Python

Invariant feature concept is added to the existing Darknet Architecture of You Only Look Once (YOLO) and is combined with Faster R-CNN to count the number of vehicles with different spatial locations.

#### 7. Predicting price based on Car specifications

Role: Developer

Technology Stack: R

Car price prediction using Multiple Linear Regression.

#### 8. Predicting People's Wellbeing

Role: Developer

Technology Stack: R

Predicted people's wellbeing based on several socio-economic factors using Naive Bayes Algorithm.

#### 9. Predicting Smoking Habits in Unknown Locations

Role: Developer

Technology Stack: R

Used k-NN model to predict smoking habits. Plotted degree of III-health using qmap.

#### 10. Predicting Academic intention to use Wikipedia

Role: Developer

Technology Stack: R

Academic Intention for Wikipedia Prediction using Naive Bayes Classifier.